Contact

laandra.elliott@mymail.barr y.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/laandra-elliott-15b4b493 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Time Management Patient Safety

Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support

Laandra Elliott

Registered Nurse at WellStar Health System Miami

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in an acute care setting. Skilled in patient-centered care, team work, collaboration, Customer Service, Time Management, and Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS in Nursing from Barry University.

Experience

WellStar Health System
Registered Nurse
November 2019 - Present (10 months)
Atlanta, Georgia

Registered Nurse in Critical Care Department

Select Specialty Hospital
Registered Nurse
October 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 2 months)

West Palm Beach, Florida Area

Experience with mechanically ventilated patients

Tracheostomy care

Performed patient centered care

Multidisciplinary collaboration

Wound care

Performing and interpreting lab results

Medication administration

Shift and focused assessment

Tracheostomy care

Interpretation of cardiac rhythm strips

Educated on critical drips, RASS, CAM-ICU, Delirium, and sepsis

Understand patient diet as well as parenteral nutrition and medication

Invasive line management and care

PIV line insertion and removal

Sterile procedures such as dressing changes, and tracheostomy suctioning

End of life care

Cultural competence

Coral Gables Hospital, Inc.
PC Technician
June 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 4 months)
coral gables, FL

Assistance and documentation of ADLs
Reinforcement of patient education
Proper body mechanics
Documentation and performing patient vital signs
Cleaning and maintaining patient comfort

Barry University
Nursing Student
August 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 1 month)
Learned nursing care
Experience in a hospital setting
Performed care plans
Performed patient assessments
Learned the anatomy, physiology, and pathophysiology of the body

Education

Barry University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing Education · (2013 - 2017)